厄尔
Hey, Earl.
全新的我们穿着全新的二手衣
It's the brand new us in brand new gently used outfits.
污渍走得可是复古风呢
The pit stains are vintage.
我这身是从垃圾桶翻出来的
I dug mine out of a dumpster.
完全没有接触到任何尿布呢
It wasn't even touching the diaper.
我看你们俩穿[自己]衣服好不习惯
I'm not used to seeing you girls in clothes.
老头子说这话 听起来更变态
Things just sound creepier when you're old.
作为餐厅的新合伙人
As new part owners of the diner,
我们要作出改进
we're making improvements.
当然不是改进食物或装修
Heh, not in the food or decor
因为 呵呵你懂的
'cause LOL.
但改进的是我们 要更美
But we're just gonna look better.
奥列格 你听说了吗
Oleg, did you hear the news?
我们以后不用穿制服上班啦
We're not wearing uniforms anymore.
好啊
Cool.
那就不穿了
Let's do it.
只要一句话
Just say the word.
内裤也是一撕就掉哦
The underwear is tear-away too.
千万别说话
Don't say words.
天啊
Oh, God!
我觉得我仿佛已经看到了他的马眼了
I think I just looked into the eye of the tiger.
我的蟑螂朋友皮埃尔来了
Oh, it's my roach friend, Pierre.
你好[法语] 皮埃尔
Bonjour, Pierre.
再见[法语] 皮埃尔
Au revoir, Pierre.
停下 趴下 打滚
Stop, drop, and roll!
你身上着火了
You're on fire.
快 磨豆腐姿势 磨磨不碍事儿
Now scissor a little. It can't hurt.
好了 现在奥列格的奶头遮起来了
Okay, now that no one can see Oleg's nipples,
我们开始吧
let's start.
你们也知道 我和麦克斯是这家餐厅的合伙人
As you know, Max and I are part owners of the diner.
你每一天都会告诉我们一遍
You been telling us every damn day
就像瘦版的布谷报时钟
like a skinny cuckoo clock.
这倒提醒我
Which reminds me,
你一提 我就该吃药了
I timed my medication to it.
我也要 厄尔
Pill me, Earl.
那是什么你就吃
What was that?
我不知道啊
I don't know.
我喜欢让我的身体玩猜猜看
Like to keep my body guessing.
开会到底要干嘛
So what's this meeting for?
宝宝快出生了
The baby's almost here
我还有很多新手爸爸该干的事没干呢
and I still have a bunch of new father stuff to do:
造一张婴儿床
build a crib;
扔掉总长55米的各式肛门拉珠
get rid of 60 yards of butt-beads.
你还会造婴儿床啊
You can build a crib?
总而言之 我们讨论的大改变是
Anyway, the big change we're talking about
现在正在换衣服呢
is changing right now.
阿憨
Han?
人家不想穿这个啦
I don't want to!
好吧好吧
Okay, fine.
这短裤看着就像廉价酒店
Those shorts look like a cheap hotel,
没有舞厅["蛋"巢]
no ballroom.
我已经失去我的餐厅了
I already lost my diner.
被羞辱得还不够吗
Haven't I been shamed enough?
多谢提醒 卡洛琳
Thanks for reminding me. Caroline?
现在够了
Now you have.
这就是你的下场 谁让你赌女子网球
And this is what you get for gambling on ladies' tennis
还欠了我们2万5啊
and owing us $25,000.
你看起来像鲍勃的"小"儿子
You look like Bob's "little" boy.
我们该直接往你嘴里点餐吗
Should we order directly into your mouth?
阿憨 现在这家餐厅是合伙人经营制
Han, since the diner is now owner operated,
如果我们得干活 那你也一样
if we have to wait on tables, so do you.
我们不在你就得替我们上班 因为我们另一家店
You're gonna cover our shifts because our other business,
甜品酒吧 还有两天就开业了
the dessert bar, is opening in two days.
你刚是不是提到你有一家甜品酒吧
Did you say you own a dessert bar?
吃药时间又到了
Huh... pill time.
你们俩就不能让我喘口气休息下吗
I don't know why I can't catch a break from you two.
麦克斯和洛城男友兰迪分手
I had to put up with Max's heartbreak
我默默忍受了她好几个月心碎不想干活
over her LA boyfriend Randy for months.
这比碧昂斯音乐电影《柠檬特调》还要宽容啊
It was more indulgent than Beyonce's "Lemonade."
-好大的胆子 -她可是女王大人
- How dare you? - She's a queen.
兰迪这个名字在餐厅里是禁忌 阿憨
The name "Randy" is off-limits in this diner, Han.
雄心壮志和新鲜牛奶也是
Like ambition or fresh milk.
姑娘们 你们逼我们出席的同时
Girls, while you have us trapped here,
我想问甜品酒吧到底是什么玩意
what the hell is a dessert bar?
是蛋糕里面有酒
Is it cake with alcohol in it?
还是酒配蛋糕啊
Or alcohol with cake?
因为无论哪种 没人会在吃完一大块馅饼后
'Cause either way, nobody wants to make love
还想做爱
after eating a big hunk of pie.
厄尔 大家都懂这个概念
Earl, everybody understands the concept.
我也搞不懂这甜品酒吧
I don't get the dessert bar thing either.
谁想听人体黄芥末酱包的意见啊
Who wants to hear from a human mustard packet?
兰迪 兰迪 兰迪 咬我啊
Randy, Randy, Randy. Zing!
靠 小矮子有辣臀啊
Damn, baby got back.
多谢你的意见 但我知道我在做什么
Thanks for the input, but I think I know what I'm doing.
我可是沃顿毕业的
I went to Wharton.
提到沃顿了
Wharton.
该吃最后一片药了
That's my last pill.
各位宝宝安安
Hey, every-baby!
没错 预产期到了
Yeah, it's my due date.
等这个宝宝出来的时间比
This baby is taking longer to come out
印第安纳州的天主教徒出柜的时间还要久
than a Catholic from Indiana.
苏菲 你有感觉到什么了吗
Sophie, do you feel anything?
除了我送给你的震动内裤之外的感觉
I mean, besides the vibrating panties I got you?
原来怪声音是那个啊
Oh, is that what that sound is?
我还以为店里飞进一只蜜蜂呢
I thought a bee got in here.
我去我的专座
Well, I'll be in my booth
等待我宝宝的降临
waiting for my baby.
欢迎来到威廉斯堡餐厅
Welcome to the Williamsburg Diner.
我是您的服务员 阿憨
I'll be your waiter, Han.
这个新妞是谁啊
Who's the new girl?
我不喜欢她
I don't like her.
这些酒保全都没有甜品酒吧的工作经验
None of these bartenders have dessert bar experience.
我猜那是因为这种酒吧是我们瞎编的
I guess that's because we made it up.
有个家伙在巧克力豆专卖店喝醉过
That one guy got drunk at the M&M's store.
能勉强搭上边吧
That's in the ballpark.
你喜欢他是因为他给你糖果了
You just like him 'cause he gave you candy.
试试又不会死
It did not hurt.
你好 我是来应聘酒保工作的
Hey. I'm here for the bartender job.
你手里没有提着你的"鸟"
Well, you're not holding your penis,
这说明你比上一个好多了
so you're doing better than the last guy.
完全公开原则 那家伙仍在候选名单中
Full disclosure: that guy's still in the running.
我也想露鸟 但我的鸟面试时会紧张
Mine would be here, but he gets nervous at interviews.
他好有趣
He's funny.
他的工作就是酒保
He's an actual bartender.
资质符合 而且还没有露鸟
He's qualified, and he's still not holding his penis.
你被雇佣了
You're hired.
欢迎加入 兰德尔
Welcome aboard, Randall.
我讨厌这个名字 人们都叫我"兰迪"
I hate that name. People call me "Randy."
我们讨厌这个名字 你可以走了
And we hate that name. Out you go.
不不不
No, no, no.
别啊 别这样
No, no, that's... come on.
他不会影响到我
He's not gonna bother me.
他跟我的兰迪完全不像
He looks nothing like my Randy.
我的兰迪
My Randy is a
如山一般高大伟岸
mountain of a man.
但生活成了我们的阻碍
But life got in the way.
他住在洛杉矶 而我要打理这家甜品酒吧
He lives in LA and I was starting this dessert bar.
唉 她仍余情未了
Yeah, she's not over it.
唉 你的名字让到嘴边的鸭子飞了
Yeah, and you really pooped the bed with the name thing.
他可以一手拎着我
He could pick me up with one arm
一手拎着中餐
and carry Chinese food with the other.
那家伙去哪儿了
Where'd that guy go?
他比亚当·兰伯特的名气消失得还快
He disappeared faster than Adam Lambert.
麦克斯 我们得避开任何会让你想到兰迪的事物
Max, we need to avoid any reminders of Randy.
我不想再次经历你抑郁的那阶段
I can't go back to that depression you were in.
那段时间我太辛苦了
It was so hard for me.
别担心
Don't worry.
我会没事的 我们也会没事的
I'll be okay and so will we.
这里可是威廉斯堡
This is Williamsburg;
随便吐个口水都能打中一个酒保
you can't spit without hitting a bartender.
或腌泡菜的人
Or an artisanal pickle maker.
我们为什么要住这里啊
Why do we live here?
我是来面试酒保的
I'm here for the bartender interview.
不是吧 居然是你俩
Oh, no, you two.
我们认识他吗
How do we know him?
等等
Wait a minute.
爸爸
Dad?
你是那个想告我们的木偶男
You're the puppet guy that tried to sue us
就在两年前 我们开第一家蛋糕店时
two years and three businesses ago
你说我们害你受伤了[第2季第17集]
by saying we injured you.
她弄坏了我的木偶
She broke my puppet.
等等 我们没有上过床啊
Wait, we never had sex.
对吧
Did we?
你是不是老爱扭啊
Do you wiggle a lot?
是的
I do.
但我们没上过床
But we didn't.
总而言之 我换了精神药物学家后
Anyway, uh, since I changed psychopharmacologists,
木偶们跟我说话的次数
the puppets aren't talking to me
变少了
as much.
这是我的简历
Here's my resume.
千万不要打给上面的介绍人
Please don't call the references.
他们都嫉妒我会说我坏话
They're all jealous of me.
特殊技能这里 你填的是"复仇"
Under special skills, you wrote, "Revenge."
哎呀 那应该是填在
Oh, whoops, that was supposed to be under
"喜爱的电视剧"那一栏
"Favorite TV Shows."
都过去了 我们能既往不咎吗
But can't we just let bygones be bygones?
说真的 我下了很大功夫改变自己
I mean, really, I've done a lot of work on myself.
我找到了内心的平和
I have found inner peace,
我通过一系列...一系列的治疗
and I've completely... completely centered myself
完全...完全集中自我
through a series of... of therapy sessions
变得超级饥渴...
that became intensely sexual.
我知道 你简历上有写
Yeah, I know. It's on your resume.
你可以打给他
Him you can call.
我们不喜欢同事是
We don't like to work with
臭人[仇人]
nemesises.
丑人
Nemesi?
这么说吧 "我们讨厌的怪人"
Let's just go with "Creepy people that we hate."
行
Fine.
你们俩皮肤白嫩
You two, with your porcelain skin
开个店了不起啊
and your businesses.
我回去继续干我那份破工作
I'll go back to my crappy daytime job,
但提醒你们一句 美国警花
but FYI, Cagney and Lacey,
没人知道甜点酒吧到底是什么鬼
nobody knows what the hell a dessert bar is.
有这么难以理解吗
What is so hard to understand?
不就是招牌鸡尾酒
It's signature cocktails
配上甜品糖果吗
paired with dessert confections.
为什么我的仇人都是天才
Why do all my enemies have to be geniuses?
他的确看起来好多了
He does seem a lot better.
麦克斯 还有两天就开业了 我们需要一个酒保
Max, we open in two days; we need a bartender.
听着 酒水这块就先交给我
Look, I will just take care of the drinks
我们会找到不叫"兰迪"的合适人选
till we find the right person not named "Randy."
麦克斯 看看这里 我们做到了
Max, look around. We did it.
只不过花光了
And it only cost every cent we got
你电影合同挣来的每一分钱而已
from your big movie deal.
还有你藏在"非大麻钱"盒子里的
And the weed money you were hiding
用来买大麻的每一分钱
in that box labeled "Not weed money."
我再去检查一下厕所
I'm gonna go check out the bathroom again.
拥有能自动冲水的马桶时 就知道自己成功了
You know you've made it when you have an industrial flush.
马桶圈是干净的 你不用撅着屁股
The seat is clean. You don't even have to hover.
这么爽
Come on!
麦克斯和卡洛琳的快递到了
Delivery for Max and Caroline.
你穿的是什么呀
What are you wearing?
我不知道为什么会这样
And I don't know how this is possible,
但你居然有骆驼趾
but you have a camel toe.
这是我的送花制服
It's my flower delivery uniform.
我多打份工 就可以快点还你俩悍妇钱
I picked up a shift so I could pay you two shrews faster
早点把餐厅弄回来
and get my diner back.
麻烦签收一下 我的自行车没锁呢
Now, could you please sign? I left my bicycle unlocked.
上面写着 "麦克斯和卡洛琳
It says, "Max and Caroline,
祝你们的甜品酒吧开张大吉 兰迪"
congratulations on your dessert bar, Randy."
这花是兰迪送的
These are from Randy.
天啊 快拿出去
Oh, my God. Get these out of here.
雏菊宝宝是我们最受欢迎的花束
The Upsy Daisies are our most popular item.
寡妇们可是为了这花大打出手呢
Widows get into fist fights over them.
爽
Yes!
阿憨 快把这花拿走
Han, get these out of here.
我不能让她看见这花 快走
I can't have her see these. Go.
我会写个批注 说你没给小费
I will make a notation that you did not tip.
你休想拿到电子优惠码
No 19-digit promo code for you.
没有信件 但走廊那个不明水坑
The mail wasn't there, but that unexplained puddle
现在越来越大了
in the hallway is thriving.
我好怕他们会称其为"泳池"
I'm afraid they're gonna call it a pool
然后以此来提高租金
and try to raise our rent.
很好啊
Good!
我也想换换环境 让朋友们来我家水坑玩
I'd love to have friends over to my puddle for a change.
我们的酒水供应许可证今天应该寄到了呀
Our liquor license was supposed to come today.
现在早应该收到信件了
We should have gotten mail by now.
我们也早该将电池
We also should have left batteries
放进一氧化碳检测器
in the carbon monoxide detector,
但我受够了那玩意一直响
but I got tired of all the beeping.
你的眼睛是不是比平时更红啊
Do your eyes feel bloodier than usual?
姑娘们
Hey, gals!
是的 没动静 我还没当妈
Yeah, nope. Still not a mother.
我好无聊啊
Oh, I'm so bored.
看完三家在线视频网站的视频了
I've Netflix'd, Hulu'd, Amazoned.
我准备要换第四家狂看了
I'm about to HBO GO out of my mind.
苏菲 这小雏菊哪儿来的
Sophie, where did you get those Upsy Daisies?
阿憨给我的
Oh, Han gave them to me.
他还试图卖给我波克诺山的一套分时度假房
Yeah, and he tried to sell me a time-share in the Poconos.
可我不得不说
Yeah, but I got to say,
我有一点点动心了
I was a little intrigued.
苏菲 你不该下来
Sophie, you shouldn't be down here.
我们这里的煤气很可能泄露了
There's a probable carbon monoxide leak.
你去看看我们的泳池吧
You should go check out our pool.
为什么阿憨要送你花
Why did Han give you flowers?
他想上你吗
Is he trying to hit that?
那他也得先够得着那里才行啊
Oh, well, he'd have to reach that first.
没有啦 这花是送给你们的
No, they were for you guys.
卡洛琳不想要
Yeah, Caroline didn't want them.
可我不介意收别人不要的花
Yeah, but I'm not above garbage flowers.
这花是兰迪送给我的
These are from Randy for me.
你居然
You!
麦克斯 我不想告诉你花的事情
Max, I didn't want to tell you about the flowers.
因为我不希望你不开心
I didn't want to upset you.
如果你不希望我不开心
If you don't want to upset me,
那你嚼沙拉的时候为什么这么大声
then why do you chew salad so loudly?
她说得有道理 卡洛琳
Uh, she's got a point there, Caroline.
我 不 生气
I am not mad.
真的吗
You're not?
真的
No.
兰迪人真好 还特地送花过来
It was really nice of Randy to send flowers
或许我该打给他
and maybe I should call him.
跟兰迪联系可不是个好主意
Bad idea to get in touch with Randy.
这主意糟透了 就像
Very bad idea, like,
小矮子穿连体裤
jumpsuits on short women.
什么
What?
他发出了善意
He did a nice thing
我只想谢谢他
and I just want to thank him.
那我们一起谢他
We'll thank him together.
你知道现在的人喜欢什么吗
You know what people like to get nowadays?
手写便条 让我拿我的信纸
A handwritten note. Let me grab my stationery.
这是一张收据 有大把地方写字
It's a Rite Aid receipt so there's plenty of room.
-亲爱的兰迪 -算了
- Dear Randy... - You know what?
打给兰迪太失礼了
Just calling Randy is rude.
你什么时候开始担心失礼这件事了
Since when do you worry about rude?
-你几乎每次都打断... -我直接跟他视频好了
- You interrupt almost every... - I want to FaceTime him.
那样更糟 你刚又打断我说话...
That's much worse, and you just interrupted me Ag...
-兰迪 -麦克斯
- Hi, Randy. - Max!
很高兴你能找我
It's so great to hear from you.
卡洛琳不在吗 还是她站在你身后
Is Caroline not there, or is she standing behind you
双臂交叉 一脸不爽
with her arms folded, looking angry?
我没有交叉双臂 我叉的是腰
My arms aren't folded, they're on my hips.
而且我没有不爽
And I'm not angry,
但麦克斯没有经过我同意就打给你
but Max called you without my permission.
你好 钱宁姐
Hi, Miss Channing.
麦克斯必须挂电话
Max has to get off the phone.
你这样我好丢脸啊
You're embarrassing me.
麦克斯 你用了整整三个月
Max, it took you three months
吃了全部口味的薯片才忘了他
and a palette of Cheetos to get over him.
你盖住的是屏幕 不是麦克风
You covered the screen, not the speaker.
你不该跟他说话
You shouldn't be talking to him.
你也不该画蓝色眼影
You shouldn't be wearing blue eye shadow.
是你说好看的
You told me it looked nice
现在小票毁了 我不能退货了
and now I've ruined the receipt and I can't take it back.
两位 我脖子要扭伤啦
Guys, I'm getting whiplash.
都不要激动好不好
You know what? Everyone just calm down.
我只是想说声谢谢
I'm just saying thank you.
搞毛啊
God-uh!
苏菲 到时间了吗
Sophie, is it time?
你要生了吗
Are you in labor?
不
No.
我自慰内裤坏了
I broke my masturbating underwear.
但你知道怎么回事吧
Ah, but you know how that goes.
我不知道
I do not
我也不会表现得我可能知道
and I will not act like I might.
你是一个
You know, you're a puzzle
我完全没兴趣解开迷
that I have no interest in solving.
你的信来了
Here's your mail.
信
The mail.
我们的酒水供应许可证
Our liquor license.
是啊
Yeah.
对了
You know what,
我觉得我的自慰内裤短路了
I think my masturbating underwear is short-circuiting,
但... 触电感觉可是相当好哟
but... eeh... oh... but it feels pretty good.
申请没通过 因为我填表时犯了个小错
Is not coming because I made a tiny mistake on the forms?
如果这话能让你好过些
Well, if it makes you feel any better,
我想说 没人知道甜品酒吧是什么鬼
nobody knows what a dessert bar is.
老实说
And frankly,
这点会让人很不爽
it just makes people angry.
麦克斯 我有个坏消息
Max, I have bad news.
天啊 你怎么没穿衣服
Oh, my God... you're naked!
我在感谢兰迪呢
I'm saying thank you to Randy.
貌似兰迪在"感谢"他自己
Looks like Randy is thanking himself.
抱歉
Oh, hey, sorry about that.
感谢的过程有点失控了
That thank you kind of got away from us.
麦克斯 把裤子穿上 我们要去市区
Max, put your pants on, we're going downtown.
真巧 兰迪刚叫我脱掉裤子
That's funny, Randy just told me
因为他也要去"湿区"
to take them off for the same reason.
我上一次看见这么长的队伍[毒品]
Last time I saw a line this long,
统统会被我吸进鼻子了
it went up my nose.
我还嗨到差点嫁给凯特·威廉姆斯
And I almost married Katt Williams.
请问一下
Excuse me?
这里有没有另一排队伍
Is there a different line for people
是专门给表上有小错 但不是填写人的错
who just made one tiny mistake and it's not her fault
是因为当时太累才填错的人排的
'cause she was just overwhelmed at the time?
麦克斯 我们要死在这里了
Max, we're gonna die here.
终于解脱了
Ugh, finally.
我本想在这里发发甜品酒吧的传单 但我刚看见
I'd give out flyers for the dessert bar, but I just saw
有人从口袋里掏出一根没包装的芝士条
someone pull an unwrapped cheese stick out of his pocket.
真不敢相信你填表也会出错
I can't believe you filled out a form wrong.
还创业呢
Start a business much?
在我看来 这算是你的错
Uh, in my defense, this is kind of your fault.
我 怎么就成了我的错了
Me? How is it my fault?
我七月大部分时间都在枕头乡里
I was in a fort made out of pillows most of July.
还是当时已经八月了
Or was it August?
我不知道 你在枕头乡会忘记时间流逝
I don't know, you can lose track of time in a fort.
没错
Exactly.
但我不得不满城跑
I had to jackass around this whole city
筹备甜品酒吧 而你却在
to get the dessert bar ready while you were
悲伤中翻滚 试图忘掉兰迪
rolling in the deep, getting over Randy.
所以
So...
来自枕头乡外的问候
hello from the other side.
妹子撕逼
Girl fight.
开撕啦
Worldstar.
事到如今 你经历了那么多
And now, after all that,
却被我抓包你和兰迪在视频激情
I catch you going down on Randy's iPhone.
我现在就警告你
I'm warning you right now,
我不会再帮你洗澡了
I am not bathing you again.
听着 有一道数学公式
Look, there is a mathematical formula
存在于分手炮里
involved in break-up sex.
你懂个屁数学啊
What do you know about math?
你连数1到10 都会忘了数6
You always leave out six when you count to ten.
那不意味着你蠢
Doesn't mean you're stupid.
很多人都会这样
A lot of persons do that.
通常来说 两人分手后
Typically, in a break-up,
如果你们住在同一个城市
if you live in the same city,
你去男方家里收拾你的东西
you go to the guy's house to pick up your stuff,
你们会打一炮
and then you do it.
这是第一炮
That's one time.
然后你"漏拿了东西" 他送到你家
Then you "forget something" and he brings it to your place
你们又会打一炮
and then you do it.
这是第二炮
That's two.
然后你们在酒吧相遇
Then you run into each other at a bar,
在厕所里打炮
do it in the bathroom.
第三炮
Three.
接着你假装怀孕 第四炮
Then you fake a pregnancy. That's four.
再接着他假装得性病 第五炮
Then he fakes an STD. That's five.
再然后你们就彻底分手了
And then you're broken up.
根本没有数学
There's been no math.
五是一个数字
Five is a number.
数字就是数学 看看书吧
Numbers are math. Read a book.
对啊 要多看书
Yeah. Read a book.
你说一本书
Name a book.
电话本[书]
The phone book.
这里只办市政许可证
This line is for municipal licenses only.
驾照 结婚证或其他的 一律不在这里
Not driver's licenses, wedding licenses, or whatnot.
只办市政许可证
Municipal licenses.
如果你不知道是什么 那你就是排错队了
If you don't know what that is, you're in the wrong line.
怎么会有人不知道
How could you not know what line
就瞎排队呢
you're supposed to be standing in?
兰迪 我等下去厕所打给你
Randy, let me call you back from the bathroom.
我知道在哪儿 我以前在这工作过
I know where it is. I used to work here.
麦克斯
Max!
卡洛琳
Hey, Caroline.
麦克斯又在因为花的事感谢我呢
Oh, Max was just thanking me for the flowers again.
所以我没有穿上衣
That's why I'm not wearing a shirt.
或裤子
Or pants.
晚点打给你 裤子先别穿上哦
Uh, let me call you back, but keep your pants off.
干嘛 这一次我不会算入五次中
What? I am not counting that as one.
你真的打算在
Were you really gonna spank it
政府办公楼打他屁股吗
in the middle of the municipal building?
打屁股
Spank it?
别这么低俗好吗 卡洛琳
Don't be crass, Caroline.
是的
Yes.
下一个
Next!
来了 来了
Ding ding ding!
应该只是笔误之类的
It's just some clerical error
我们应该今天就可以拿到许可证了
so we should be able to get our license today.
让我来处理
Let me handle this.
毕竟你也知道你过去有
You know you have a history of
碰到官老爷就犯二的历史
getting slappy with bureaucrats.
您好
Hi.
我们收到这封信
We got this in the mail,
里面貌似有个小小的错误
and there's been some teensy little mistake...
哎哟哟
Well, well, well!
这货
Him!
莫伊莎 放着我来
I've got this, Moesha.
你何不去清理一下
Why don't you go clean up your little
微波炉里你弄出来的速冻食品残渣呢
Lean Cuisine explosion in the microwave?
她可邋遢了
Oh, she's a mess.
我能怎么
Now, how can I
给两位帮倒忙呢
not help you two?
这就是你说的没出路工作吗
This is your dead-end job?
我还想象你是去当运毒人
I pictured you working as a drug mule
或脱口秀节目充场面的观众呢
or a seat filler on The View.
那也叫工作吗
That's a job?
兄弟 我就只是申请表上填错了
Dude, I just made a mistake on the application.
能不能放我们一马
Can't you just give us a break?
我们的甜品酒吧本来应该明晚开幕
Our dessert bar is supposed to open tomorrow night.
求你了
Please?
我为了这生意放弃了我男朋友
I gave up a boyfriend for this business,
如果这事黄了
and I'm gonna mess up
我一定会把她这张美颜划个稀巴烂
her pretty face if it doesn't work out.
麦克斯 谢谢你
Max, thank you.
我本来还开始觉得你认为我没那么好看呢
I was starting to think you didn't think I was that pretty.
如果我们不搞定这事 我们开幕就得延后了
If we don't fix this, we're gonna have to delay our opening.
求求你了
So please?
这样吧
You know what?
我跟我上司谈谈
Let me talk to my supervisor.
他的脖子有些僵硬了
His neck's a little rusty,
但他摇头了
but that's a no.
我想给咱俩调杯酒 但没有许可证
I would make us a drink but without a liquor license,
我唯一能做的只有冰毒
all I can make is meth.
这全是我的错
This is all my fault.
不是 是我因为兰迪变成废人
No, I was in a funk about Randy
所以你得自己张罗各种大小事
and you had to do all this stuff on your own.
-是我的错 -好吧 太好了
- It's my fault. - Okay, good.
这才是我真实想法
That's what I really thought,
但我想确定咱俩都这么想
but I just wanted to make sure it was out there.
麦克斯 我们毫无运气 屁点没有
We have zero luck, Max, zero.
我就顺便过来说一句
I just stopped by to say
甜品酒吧的事我也很遗憾
I'm sorry about your dessert bar.
你俩倒霉到"像屎"啊
You two are unlucky A, F.
是"像屎迪哥"
That's "As Freddie."
他是我的朋友
He's a friend of mine.
他就倒霉到不行
He's very unlucky.
厄尔
Earl,
不能从外面带酒
there's no outside liquor.
因为这会让我们感觉更糟糕
'Cause it just makes us feel worse.
这不是外面带的酒 这是餐厅的
This ain't outside liquor. It's from the diner.
从酒上飘的牛肉碎 你看不出吗
Can't you tell by the beef floating in it?
天啊 这不是外面带的酒
Oh, my God. It's not from outside.
是从餐厅内部
It's from the diner.
麦克斯 餐厅老板是谁
Max, who owns the diner?
我 你 还有一只亚洲松鼠
Me, you, and an Asian squirrel.
麦克斯 我们不需要再申请许可证因为...
Max, we don't need a liquor license because...
我们已经有一个了
We already have one.
我又做了一道数学题
Oh! I just did more math.
这也不算数学
Still not math!
我上一次看女人跑这么快
I haven't seen women move that fast
是酸奶出现细菌污染被召回那次
since the Activia recall.
找到了
Here it is!
天啊 阿憨的中间名是玛格丽特
Oh, my God, Han's middle name is Margaret.
想不到天上真的会掉馅饼啊
Sometimes the universe just gives you a gift.
凡持有该证的老板 经营者 经营者们...
This entitles the owner, operator, operators...
就是我们
That's us!
威廉斯堡餐厅的经营者
...of the Williamsburg Diner
有权贩卖酒类给21岁以上顾客
to serve alcohol to those persons 21 and over,
以及不卖酒类商品给
reserving the right to not serve those persons
不能出示有效证件客人
who do not supply valid ID!
麦克斯 你知道这代表什么意思吗
Max, do you know what this means?
我绝对要在憨·玛格丽特
I am totally carding Han Margaret
来甜品酒吧时 检查他证件
when he comes in our dessert bar,
我们酒吧明晚绝对能开幕
which is so opening tomorrow night.
各位宝宝安安
Hey, every-baby.
还怀着...
Still preg... achoo!
你们也看到这个了吗
Are you guys seeing this too?
我这辈子都忘不掉了
I'm never gonna forget it.
我的羊水好像破了
I think my water broke.
奥列格
Oleg!
快拿水桶拖把出来
Get out here and bring the mop bucket.
苏菲要生了
Sophie's in labor.
我现在就打电话叫车
Oh. I'm calling the car right now.
上面写着"你的司机已到"
It says "Your Lyft driver is already here."
有人叫车吗
Did somebody order a car?
是女演员明妮·德里弗[迷你司机]
Look, it's Minnie Driver.
苏菲 我们的孩子要出世啦
Sophie, we're having a baby.
我好怕
I'm scared.
她的确该怕
She should be scared,
她穿着通电内裤呢
she's wearing electric underwear.
慢慢来 深呼吸
Slow, easy breaths.
我有啊
I am!
我其实是在跟自己说啦
I was more talking to myself.
别丢下我一个人啊
Don't leave me in there alone.
明知道我快死 现在都能看到鬼了
You know I see dead people.
要来了
It's coming.
就要来了
It's coming!
到了
It's here!
孩子吗
The baby?
的确来了个"孩子"
Well, a baby.
好了 我们的"幼"步司机到了
Oh, good, our goober driver's here.
为了从你俩手上赎回餐厅
Aren't I suffering enough
我受的苦还不够吗
to get the diner back from you two?
我已经同时是滴滴和优步的司机
I'm already driving for Lyft and Uber
副驾杂物箱里还有兼职卖的摇头丸呢
and selling Molly out of that glove compartment.
我要坐副驾
Shotgun!
阿憨 我不想说亚洲女司机车技都烂
Han, I hate to hit the stereotype of Asian women drivers,
但你他娘的能不能开快点
but could you speed the hell up?
你们是想快点到达
Do you want to arrive quickly
还是想要安全到达
or do you want to arrive safely?
放个泰迪熊你开毛多人车道啊 死婆娘
A teddy bear doesn't count as carpooling, lady!
我孩子不能是车生儿
I can't have a car baby.
我三个兄弟都是车上出生的
Three of my brothers were born in the car.
都是在去森林的路上
On the way to the woods,
他们本应该在森林里出生
where they were supposed to be born.
苏菲 你的座位能不能往前拉一点
Sophie, do you think you could move your seat up a scooch?
只因我腿已压骨折
Only because I think my leg is broken.
这让我想起有次公路旅行
This reminds me of a road trip I took one time
我跟大地风火乐团的人一起
with Earth, Wind & Fire.
结果因为车上太挤
The car was so cramped,
我们只好先放"风"下车
we had to leave Wind behind.
我觉得车上的某人屁股也放了"风"
I feel like someone just left some wind behind in here.
敢打灯吗
Signal much?
苏菲 冲镜头笑一个
Sophie, smile for the camera.
我不想错过任何一秒
I don't want to miss a minute.
我家族的男人还没有过任何一个
No Golishevsky man has ever been there
是孩子出世时在身边陪着的
for the birth of his child.
为啥 是因为看到
Why, because it's bad luck
自己的老婆出生会带来霉运吗
to see your wife before she's born?
跟人分享自己的叔叔娶了他女儿的故事
You tell one story where your uncle marries his daughter,
突然之间 自己就被人当乱伦男
and suddenly, you're the incest guy.
惨了
Uh-oh.
真要生了
It's happening.
我能感觉到宝宝的脑袋
Ah, I can feel the baby's head.
是你的潜艇堡啊
It's your sandwich.
送你吧
It's yours now.
好吧
All right.
苏菲 你得撑到医院啊
Sophie, you have to make it to the hospital.
我卖了我世面罕见的脚趾控黄片
I sold my rare toe-porn collection
订了高档产房呢
to pay for a fancy birthing suite.
我要很有范儿地生下这孩子
I'm gonna give birth to this baby in style.
毕竟生完不需要担心有野生动物袭击
I won't have to protect it from wild animals afterwards,
这感觉太好了
you know, which is nice.
苏菲 别在高档产房里待舒爽了才生
Sophie, don't get too comfortable in that suite.
一到医院就把孩子像
You're gonna need to drop it like it's hot
拉开插销的手榴弹一样扔出来
the second we get to the hospital.
我和麦克斯还得给甜品酒吧开幕做准备呢
Max and I have to get ready for our dessert bar opening.
车上有婴儿 挡我者死
Baby on board! Move it or lose it!
替他们辩解下 他们看不出这车是有人驾驶的
In their defense, it looks like no one's driving this car.
不好意思 医生 已经12小时了
Excuse me, doctor? It's been 12 hours.
有没有什么方法能加速一下
Is there some way we could speed this up?
比如让她开合跳 吃印度菜拉出来
You know, jumping jacks, Indian food,
或剖腹产
a C-section?
她有在场的需要吗
Does she need to be in here?
有吧
Yeah.
这妞
Yeah, that one
跟那边那妞 是这孩子的干妈
and the other one over there are the godparents.
麦克斯
Max.
加油啊 老姐
Yeah, girl.
她们不是一对
They're not a couple.
虽然奥列格觉得她们有一点拉拉倾向
Oleg thinks they do it a little though.
只开了一公分 还是没有出来的迹象
Only 1 centimeter. I don't feel anything.
估计还得一阵
It could be a while.
苏菲 你最好把束腹裤脱了吧
Sophie, you may want to take off the Spanx.
我只是怀孕
I'm pregnant.
又不是死了
I'm not dead.
坐浴缸脚麻了
Oh, man, tub legs.
我会再回来
I'll be back.
不过不是因为我想回来
But not because I want to.
奥列格 赶紧啊 拍下这产房
Oleg, come on, film the room.
我想要孩子知道我们给她女王般待遇
I want our baby to know that I was treated like a queen.
我记得艾尔顿·约翰生孩子的时候
You know, I think Elton John had this room
好像就是在这间生的
when he gave birth.
抱歉 我刚才找不到你们
I'm sorry, I lost y'all.
我在轮床上睡着 醒来发现被人推到停尸间了
I feel asleep on a gurney and woke up in the morgue.
我把一票医科学生给吓尿了
I scared the pants off a bunch of med students.
我的闹钟响了
Ooh, there's my alarm.
我得去跟我的前男友兰迪打电话分手炮了
I have to go have break-up phone sex with my ex, Randy.
就像你们一样
Like you do.
别走太远
Well, don't go very far 'cause
奥列格在医院
Oleg gets fainty in hospitals
跟那些卖丑衣服的超市会头晕
and supermarkets that also sell clothing.
太难以接受了
It's just too much.
麦克斯你跟兰迪打过的分手炮
Max, you and Randy have had more sex since your break-up
比我跟我大学男友"做"过的还多次
then I had with my college boyfriend.
虽然他是因为当年醉心于音乐剧
Granted, he was very busy with musical theater.
我们唯一一次做爱 是他穿着《猫》的戏服
The only time we had sex was when he was in his Cats' costume
并让我以剧中帅猫身份来"宠幸"他
and he asked me to give him a Rum Tum Tugger.
规矩就是
The rule is
在正式分手前得"做"足足五次
you have sex five times before you're broken up.
而这是第五次
And this is number five.
根据过往经验 最盛大 汗水淋漓
Historically, the biggest, sweatiest,
最以菊花为中心的一次
and the most butt-centric...
他的 不是我的
his, not mine.
所以
So...
请勿打扰
Do not disturb.
你平板拿反了 画面十分恶心人[打扰]
It's facing the wrong way, and it's very disturbing.
兰迪 你好啊
Hey, Randy.
抱歉 我... 刚起床
Oh, sorry, I just, uh, just woke up.
感觉你已经"起立"一段时间啦
Looks like you've been up for awhile.
不介意我去你裤裆"帐篷"里待吧
Mind if I camp under that pup tent?
你能去别的地方烤他的"串儿"吗
Can you go roast his marshmallows somewhere else?
不好意思 有个超超超级贵宾要来
Excuse me, there's a VVVIP patient coming in
他们要求清出这间
who needs this room.
我才不管他们是有啥病
I don't care what kind of disease they have.
老娘哪都不去
I'm not going.
天啊
Oh, my God.
是超模瓦妮莎·妮波迪托
That's supermodel Vanessa Nibotito.
她又漂亮又聪明
She's pretty and smart.
两者兼具很难吧 姐妹
It's hard, right girl?
我付钱订了这间房呢
I... I paid for this room.
那一大袋硬币是我们付的啊
That giant bag of quarters? That's us!
我的宝宝真的要被山寨版的我
Is my baby bump seriously getting bumped
给挤去别间病房了吗
by a poor man's me?
太对不住了
I'm so sorry.
有兴趣我可以叫人送你一本我的怀孕全纪录
I could send you a copy of my motherhood book if you'd like.
我请的代笔写得可好了
The lady I paid to write it did a great job.
等等 等等 不要 我哪都不去
Oh, wait... wait a minute, no... I'm not going anywhere.
不要 等等
No, wait a minute.
等等 我不要走 我不要
Wait, I'm not... no, I'm not going.
你们不能逼我 别啊
You can't make me. No, wait a minute.
等等 等等 稍等一下
Wait a min... oh, wait, wait, wait.
你们看 我在这还能做点手部锻炼呢
Oh, look, I'm getting a little arm workout here.
苏菲 医院说他们把我们赶出病房
Sophie, the hospital is saying they bounced us from the room
是因为我们拖太长时间了
because we took too long.
给我们一张重症监护室烧烫伤科旁的小床
They're offering us a cot near the burn unit of the ICU.
好吧
Well,
看来[重症监护室]的人不知道
ICU don't understand that I'm not having this baby
我没回到那间房是不会生的
until I get back in my suite.
克里斯 她打死也不要
That's a hard "No," Chris.
猜猜谁调情骗来了免费的腕管综合症手套
Guess who just flirted her way into a free carpal tunnel glove?
某些女孩调情勾引干爹
Some girls flirt their way into a sugar daddy;
而我则是免费医疗用品
I get medical supplies.
好消息不止如此
And more good news...
你把我病房要回来了吗
Did you get me my room back?
那段好日子已经过完了
No, those days are over.
咱们现在是走廊游民的命
We're hallway people now.
但我趁机给甜品酒吧打印了传单
But I was able to print out flyers for our dessert bar.
我想给传单弄成圆边
I'd love to give them a rounded edge.
你有剪刀吗
Do you have scissors?
你是不是闹呢
Are you kidding me?
我当然有啦 我包里给你找
Of course I do. Look in my bag.
苏菲 他们愿意给我们完整大小病床
Sophie, they're offering us a full-size bed,
但是是在核磁共振机里
but it's in an MRI machine.
我觉得我们该接受
I think we should take it.
甜品酒吧今晚开幕
Dessert bar opening tonight.
我们有轮椅专道
We have a ramp.
不好意思 借过 借过
Excuse me, coming through. Coming through.
有大牌病人要生了
A-lister about to give birth.
天啊
Oh, my God.
明星医生 南希·刚萨雷斯
Celebrity doctor, Nancy Gonzales!
我喷的就是你出的香水呢
You know, I wear your perfume.
南希 你可能有听说 甜品酒吧今晚开幕
Nancy, you might have heard, dessert bar opening tonight.
来个人管管这些走廊游民
Someone needs to control the hallway people.
兰迪
Randy.
麦克斯
Max!
不是我 是调皮护士旺达
That wasn't me, it was naughty nurse Wanda.
正打算给旺达"来一针"
I was about to give Wanda a shot.
应该说是她要给自己"来一针"
Well, she was gonna give it to herself,
只不过我会指导她准确该怎么"做"
but I was gonna tell her exactly how to do it.
麦克斯 在医院玩色情医生俏护士
Max, isn't playing doctor in a hospital
也太没哏了吧
a little on the nose?
我喜欢有个主题嘛
I like to be on theme.
如果是在海鲜速食餐厅
We can play pirate and lusty wench
我也能跟他玩淫荡海盗娇村姑啊
when I'm in a Long John Silver's.
你不能 因为我们就是因为这原因
No, you won't because we're not allowed in there
上了店里的黑名单
for that very reason.
而且你不是已经搞过第五次了吗
Plus, didn't you already have your fifth time?
卡洛琳 是这样的 洛城的分手炮是6次
You see, Caroline, break-up sex in LA is six times.
明星夫妻雷亚与德维托的规矩
It's the DeVito-Perlman rule.
雷亚闹分手时回家拿瑜伽毯 五瓶甜酒下肚
Rhea forgot her yoga mat, and five limoncellos later,
一炮
boom!
剩下的就是过往云烟了
The rest is history.
他是律师 所以我们得听他的
He's a lawyer so we have to listen to him.
甜品酒吧今晚开幕
Dessert bar opening tonight.
苏菲 你下面有点动静了吗
Sophie, any progress in your nethers?
我们甜品酒吧再五小时要开幕了
'Cause our dessert bar opens in five hours,
而传单上写了我本人保证会在现场
and it promises I'll be there on the flyer.
甜品酒吧今晚开幕 我会在场哦
Dessert bar opening tonight. I'll be there.
你真的要把自己称呼为
Did you really have to refer to yourself as
"纽约招牌卡洛琳·钱宁"吗
"New York's Own Caroline Channing"?
她要出来了 走廊游民 闪开
She's coming. Hallway people, clear a path.
恭喜你啊
Congratulations
因为你被邀请出席甜品酒吧开幕
because you're invited to our dessert bar opening.
你可以带你的婴儿一起来
You can bring the baby if you want,
不过我不会太高兴
but I wouldn't love it.
甜点是什么
What's dessert?
我还是要发微博说她会来
I'm still tweeting that she's coming.
我要把这间病房抢回来了 姑娘们
I'm taking the suite back, girls.
推我进去
Roll me in!
没错 我们又不是走廊游民啦
Yeah, we're not hallway people anymore.
寿司可以放多久不坏
How long can sushi be sitting out?
没多久
Ooh, not that long.
那这个呢
What about this one?
麦克斯 别啊
Max, don't.
传单上也保证了
It promises on the flyer
你到时候也会在甜品酒吧开幕现场
that you'll be at the dessert bar opening too.
虽然用的字号比较小 但还是有写啊
It's in smaller letters, but it's there.
我尽最快速度赶来了
Oh. I got here as fast as I could.
来把宝宝接生出来吗
To take the baby out?
不 是来看超模啊
No, to see the model.
她已经走了
Um, she's gone.
她一直念叨"哥穆尔卡医生在哪"
She kept saying, "Where's Doctor Gomulka?"
她真叫我了吗
Really?
没有 永远不会有人这么说
No, no one's ever said that.
反正已经失望至极
Well, since I'm already disappointed,
我就再看一眼单子底下吧
I guess I'll take a look under the hood.
奥列格 你知道我很喜欢
Oleg, you know how I love to have a snack
被检查时吃零食吗
when I get my exam.
我这就去礼品店给你买一些
I'll go to the gift shop and grab you some
巧克力坚果包跟口香糖
chocolate-heavy trail mix and some Hubba Bubba.
奥列格
Oh, and Oleg!
把袋子反过来然后...
Turn the bag upside down and... oh.
他懂我要求
He knows.
如果我是个赌徒 我大概会赌
Well, if I were a gambling man, I'd say
至少五小时后出生吧
it'll be at least five hours.
我就是这么赌输掉我房子的
And that's how I lost my house.
护士 我需要东西剪脐带
Nurse, I need something to cut the umbilical cord.
等等 等等
Oh, I... wait, wait.
你运气真好
You're in luck.
苏菲
Sophie,
你太棒了
you did great.
你现在是个母亲了
You're a mother.
祝你健康
Also, gesundheit.
宝宝真好看
Aw, the baby's beautiful.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我把孩子生下来了
I had the baby!
而奥列格错过了这一刻
And Oleg missed it.
他一早就下定决心要看着孩子出世
Oh, and he had his heart set on seeing the baby being born.
结果他错过了
And he missed it.
他永远不会原谅自己
He's never gonna forgive himself!
他永远永远永远永远永远永远...
He's never, never, never, never, never, never...
别这样 苏菲 冷静
Please, Sophie, calm down.
或许奥列格没错过
Maybe Oleg didn't miss it.
你对科学的无知好让我担心啊
It worries me how little you know about science stuff.
我们可以来一场假生产嘛
We'll fake the birth.
你是在叫我帮忙搞一场假生产吗
You're asking me to help you fake a birth?
你能行 你都假高潮过了
You'll be fine. You've faked an orgasm.
好吧 的确
Well, that's true.
我们得想办法让奥列格晕过去够长时间
We have to make Oleg pass out long enough to bring
才能把宝宝抱回来 再让他以为
the baby in and make him think he just missed
他其实只是走神了一下子
a second of the actual birth.
苏菲 快假装你要生了
Sophie, act like you're in labor.
就大叫 然后说早知道就不该认识奥列格
Just yell and tell Oleg you wish you never met him.
应该很好演
It should be easy.
他来了 各就各位
He's coming. Places.
抱歉这么久才回来 但我排我前面的女人
Sorry it took so long, but the lady in front of me
要用背书转让支票来付软糖钱
paid for her Jujubes with a third-party check.
我好疼啊
Oh, I'm in pain!
我要生下孩子啦
Oh, I'm about to have a baby
第一次呢
for the first time!
好了 我准备好了
Okay. I'm ready.
我随手拿了罐东西喝 现在我意识到
I popped a Pepto and what I'm now realizing
那是泻药
was a laxative.
奥列格
Oleg,
快躲到溅射范围外
you stay out of the splash zone.
要生啦
It's go time.
这底下有好些触目惊心不忍直视的东西
Oh, there is some seriously birthy stuff going on down here.
要不要去叫医生来啊
Oh, should we get a doctor?
没男的叫女的也好
Even a girl one?
没时间了
There's no time!
各种恶心分泌物大量喷出
Because of all the oozing gunk!
用力 苏菲 用力
Push, Sophie, push!
你 你 你个贱人
You... you... you...
都是你的害的
you did this to me
用你让我爽翻天的肉棒害惨我
with your gorgeous penis!
我跟他都很对不起
We're both sorry!
麦克斯 下面还有什么恶心的状况吗
Max, anything else disgusting going on down there?
这下面的状况简直要恶心死人啊
Oh, yeah, we got a real sick situation here.
天啊 好多胎盘粘液
Oh, man, there's a lot of placenta goo.
我上次这么晕是进了一家超大型廉价超市
I haven't been this woozy since I was in a Super Target.
我不会晕倒的
I'm not going down.
我打死不晕
湿哒哒黏糊糊的宝宝正在努力通过粘液
The wet, sludgy baby is fighting through the slime!
姑娘们 快点
Oh, girls, quick.
他晕了 快去抱孩子过来
He's down. Get the baby!
天啊 好了
Oh, my God. All right.
行了 现在把他弄醒吧
All right, now, to wake him up,
喊"移民局"或痒他的...
yell "Immigration" or tickle his...
移民局来啦
Immigration!
我错过什么了
What'd I miss?
你看 奥列格
Look, Oleg.
宝宝生下来啦
The baby is here.
是闺女
And it's a girl.
她也有个小洞洞 就像她妈妈
She has a bejoonie, just like her mama.
她真漂亮 就像她妈妈
She's beautiful, just like her mama.
是啊
Yeah.
你想抱她吗
Do you want to hold her?
真的吗
Yeah?
真的
Yeah.
你看
Look.
他是你爸爸
That's your daddy.
等她熟悉了这世界
Let her get settled in the world
再开始告诉她坏消息吧
before you start giving her bad news.
宝宝 你好
Hello, baby.
芭芭拉
Barbara!
芭芭拉·科臣斯基·高列彻夫斯基
Barbara Kuchenski Golishevsky!
听起来很有旋律感 对吧
Oh, that sounds real musical, doesn't it?
看你都听哪种音乐了
Depends what kind of music you listen to.
她好可爱啊
Aww, she's so cute.
真确定叫芭芭拉了吗
Barbara's a definite?
对啊
Yeah.
我是你干妈
I'm your godmother.
有一天我会教你怎么撒谎骗这两人
One day I'm gonna teach you how to lie to these two.
还有这个人
And also this one.
看看这么多人等在我们门外
Look at all those people at our door.
而且没人带着火把要寻仇
And not a torch in the mix.
厄尔 你又走丢了吗
Oh, Earl. Are you lost again?
餐厅是在隔壁
The diner is next door!
别害他搞混 他是我们酒吧看门人
Don't confuse him. He's our bouncer.
你是我们酒吧看门人
You're our bouncer!
你不会真指望你名单上所有人
Now, you don't really expect everybody on this list
都会出席开幕式吧
to show up, now, do you?
利亚姆·海姆斯沃斯跟我微博上在撕逼呢
'Cause Liam Hemsworth and I are in a Twitter feud.
好吧 名单上有几个的确是有点痴心妄想
Okay, some of it may have been wishful thinking,
但我给二链子发短信了
but I did text 2 Chainz.
我们有一次跟他在私人飞机上遇见
We met him on a private plane once.
我给了他我的号码
I gave him my digits.
二链子 是人名还是种着装方式
Uh, 2 Chainz, is that a person or a dress code?
两者皆是
It's both.
厄尔 二链子是知名饶舌歌手
Earl, 2 Chainz is a famous rapper.
天啊 二链子来了
Oh, my God, 2 Chainz is here... ah!
我要让知名饶舌歌手二链子在我们开幕前进来
I'm letting 2 Chainz the famous rapper in before we open.
最近好吗 琳琳
What's up, Double C?
她比较喜欢被人称呼"纽约招牌大波琳妹妹"
She prefers to be called, "New York's Own Double C."
最近好吗
Sup?
真不敢相信你真的来我们甜品酒吧
I can't believe you made it to our dessert bar.
我真不敢相信有人知道甜品酒吧是什么
I can't believe anybody knows what a dessert bar is.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding?
糖与酒最搭了
Sugar and alcohol go hand in hand.
两种美妙滋味合而为一
It's two great tastes that taste great together.
就像我完美融合了新派与老派的旋律
Like how I seamlessly fuse new-school and old-school flows.
现在我能理解了
Well, now I get it.
你们为什么不这么跟我解释呢
Why didn't you just say that, girls?
我能来一杯果馅马丁尼吗 麻烦啦
Now, can I get one of those flan-tinis, please?
二链子 抱歉我之前没认出你
Look, sorry I didn't recognize you, 2 Chainz.
我的音乐杂志1984年到期后就没续订了
I let my subscription to Vibe expire in 1984.
没事的
Oh, that's okay.
他们好像有给回头客折扣
I think they give discounts for return customers.
真的吗
Oh, really?
哎哟哟
Well, well, well!
看看谁在我
Look who opened up a bar
拒批许可证后开了家酒吧啊
after I denied them a liquor license.
哎哟哟 看看是谁
Well, well, well, look who decided
穿了女人裤子 还希望没人会发现啊
to wear ladies' pants hoping no one would notice.
劫佩托 你来干嘛
J. Petto, what are you doing here?
你怎么知道我们今天开幕
How did you know we were opening?
我绝对没给你发过传单
I definitely didn't give you a flyer.
我有粉二链子的微博
I follow 2 Chainz on Twitter,
有时候也在车里跟踪[粉]他
sometimes in my car.
告诉你 我一键就能打给警察
Just so you know, I have 911 on speed dial.
这是我们的酒水许可证
Our liquor license, sir.
这是威廉斯堡餐厅的酒牌
Uh, this belongs to the Williamsburg Diner.
他们属于同家店 餐厅也是我们的
They're the same property. We own the diner.
两家店同出一脉
They're related,
就像帅大叔亚历克·鲍德温跟最丑的
like Alec and whoever the grossest Baldwin is.
丹尼尔·鲍德温是兄弟
Daniel.
你不能用其他生意的酒水许可证
You can't use another establishment's liquor license.
我要勒令你们关闭
I'm shutting you two down
我还要罚款餐厅的老板
and I'm slapping the owner of the diner
两万五千元罚款
with a $25,000 fine.
这个贱人到底是谁
Who is this bitch?
就是个卑贱小人
Just some mean, little man with
大周五晚上没事干 就要跑来毁我们人生
nothing better to do on a Friday night than ruin our lives.
才不是 这里完事后我还得
Not true; I'm taking my aunt
带我阿姨去变性人宾果游戏呢
to drag bingo right after this.
姑娘们
Well, girls,
这狗搞遍全绿点区的母狗后
I managed to make it here after this dog fornicated
才肯跟我过来这里
his way across Greenpoint.
我去过
Been there.
我搞过
Done that.
这里是三百块
Here's $300.
这是我打了12份工
My earnings after working 12 jobs
又被抢劫过4次后剩下的钱
and being robbed 4 times.
被同一个女的抢了两次
Twice by the same girl.
你可以要回你的餐厅
You can have your diner back.
我们不忍心从你手里抢走餐厅
We feel bad about taking it from you,
而且餐厅的老板得付
and also the owner of the diner owes
老屁股下巴哥跟市政府两万五罚款
old butt-chin here and the city $25,000.
什么
What?
餐厅又是我的啦
The diner is mine again?
对啊 抱歉
Yeah, sorry.
太好啦
Yes!
太好啦 太好啦
Yes! Yes!
我的宝宝又回到我手里啦
I have my baby back.
你全身哪里不是宝宝大小
You have baby everything.
我要勒令你们关门14个工作日
I'm shutting you down for 14 business days.
而你会收到一封罚款信
And you're getting a bill in the mail
上面还会有非常让人不解的指示
with very confusing instructions.
还有
And...
我要在这里办我的生日会
I'm having my birthday here.
咱们走 二链子
Let's bounce, 2 Chainz.
再见啦 兄弟
So long, pal.
你得找别人来当你的磨牙玩具了
You're gonna have to find someone else to use as a chew toy.
好吧
Oh, man.
酒吧的事真遗憾啊 姑娘们
Sorry about the bar, girls.
看来我只能跟你外带瓶酒
I mean, guess I'm gonna have to get me a bottle of rose
然后去费尔斯太太饼干店里喝了
and head over to Mrs. Fields' again.
她有姐妹吗
Does she have a sister?
或者是彩色电视呢
Or a color TV?
再见啦 姑娘们
See you later, girls.
看来我得跟这位老先生一起去派对啦
It look like I'm gonna go party with the old man right here.
各位能再多等我们一会
Can you guys just give us another minute?
或者14个工作日吗
Or 14 business days?
唯一比我们还短命的大概只有
The only thing that opened and closed faster than us
不卖座电影《威士忌 探戈 狐步舞》了
was Whiskey, Tango, Foxtrot.
幸好我没特别花钱去弄头发
Well, at least I didn't get a blow out for this.
让开幕失败所带来的伤痛轻了一点
That lessens the sting of a failed opening.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
我觉得这会让我们更炙手可热
I think this is gonna make us more popular.
人永远都会想要他们得不到的东西
You know how people always want what they can't have.
就像你想要所有东西一样
Like you with everything.
如果这是真的 你为什么看起来很难过
If that's true, then why do you look upset?
因为我跟兰迪真的彻底分手了
'Cause Randy and I are really broken up.
各种分分合合的明星夫妻条款
We burned through the Affleck-Garner clause,
或者招数都被我们拿来用过了
the Cox-Arquette addendum.
直到最终我们要用比伯跟戈麦斯原则时
As soon as we got to the Bieber-Gomez principle,
我们都看不起自己了才结束
we were ashamed of ourselves.
麦克斯 你可是破坏规矩界的女王
Max, you're the queen of not following the rules.
你不是说"规矩 屁矩"吗
"Rules, schmules," You say.
对啊
Yes!
规矩 屁矩
Rules, schmules!
还有保险套 屁险套
And condoms, schmondoms.
这个就不怎么样
Yeah, that one's not great.
我的意思是你总自己想出新东西
What I'm saying is you make stuff up.
就像这个甜品酒吧
Like this dessert bar.
而这是个很棒的点子
And that was a great idea.
所以你也应该为你和兰迪定个新规矩
So you should make up rules for you and Randy.
因为感觉你们真的很在乎彼此啊
'Cause it really seems like you guys care about each other.
好吧 你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
分手 分屁手
Break-up, schmake-up.
去吧 打给兰迪
Now, go call Randy
恶心到我想烧掉我的平板吧
and make me want to burn my iPad.
去吧 求你了
Go, I'm begging you.
我们绝对会大展宏图
Yeah, we're gonna kill it
只要再等14个工作日就行了
in 14 business days.